smartonlineprofitsystems.com.au 2009-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Smart Online Profit Systems

## Privacy Policy

Geekdom Pty Limited ( **Geekdom** ), as part of Photon Group Limited, is committed to adopting the highest standards to safeguard our customers’ personal information.

Geekdom, like other companies operating in Australia, is bound by the National Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000.

Throughout this policy, we refer to your ‘personal information’ which means information which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your mail address is an example of personal information.

Geekdom’s collection, use and disclosure of personal information is set out below.

**What Personal Information does Geekdom collect and why?**

Geekdom collects personal information about you in order to provide personalized internet marketing education and information services.

The personal information you provide to Geekdom will enhance the products and services that we offer to you. The type of personal information we collect may include your name, address, telephone numbers, information on how you use our products and services (such as the seminars you attend and information on your browsing activity when visiting our website) and personal preferences. This information permits us to develop products and services to suit your needs.

**How may Geekdom use your personal information?**

The personal information you provide Geekdom may be used for a number of purposes connected with our business operations, which include:

  * processing your orders or applications;
  * carrying out credit checking (unless we have agreed otherwise);
  * providing you with products and/or services requested;
  * billing you or administering your account;
  * dealing with requests, enquiries or feedback and other customer care related activities;
  * carrying out market and product analysis and marketing our products and services generally;
  * contacting you about our Geekdom’s product, services and promotions;
  * carrying out any activity in connection with a legal, governmental or regulatory requirement on us or in connection with legal proceedings, crime or fraud prevention, detection or prosecution.

We may also use your personal information for purposes related to those described above which would be reasonably expected by you. For example, we may use your personal information to keep you informed about features of our internet marketing education services or conducting analysis in order to provide better service to you. To opt-out of receiving certain Geekdom marketing materials, please send an email to [unsubscribe( at )geekversity.com](mailto:unsubscribe\(%20at%20\)geekversity.com). Please note that Geekdom will still need to send you essential information about your account or changes to your service.

We will not use your information for purposes other than described above unless we have your consent or there are specified law enforcement reasons.

**How may Geekdom share your personal information?**

Geekdom may disclose or receive personal information or documents about you to/from:

  * credit providers or credit reporting agencies for the purposes permitted under the Privacy Act;
  * law enforcement agencies to assist in the prevention of criminal activities;
  * our service and content providers, dealers and agents, or any company within the Photon Group for purposes that are related to providing you with an internet marketing education service which would be reasonably expected.

Unless you consent, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties, other than those who have contracted with Geekdom to keep the information confidential, or who are subject to obligations to protect your personal information.

**Security of your personal information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

**How can you access your personal information?**

Upon your request, Geekdom will take reasonable steps to let you know, generally, what sort of personal information we hold, for what purposes and how we collect, use and disclose that information.

Upon your request, Geekdom will provide access to your personal information we hold, except in certain prescribed circumstances, including emergency situations, specified business imperatives and law enforcement or other public interests.

**How to contact us**

If you have any queries or concerns, please contact Customer Care by emailing [support( at )geekversity.com](mailto:support\(%20at%20\)geekversity.com).
